Godwin Odenigbo

Fullstack Blockchain Developer

London, United Kingdom. | +447448196391 | godwintrav@gmail.com

Summary

I am a Fullstack Blockchain Developer with two years experience developing industry standard Web2 and Web3 Applications.

Strong in design and integration problem-solving skills.

I am an expert in smart contract development using solidity and backend development with database analysis and design using Node.js and NoSQL.

Strong written and verbal communications, focused and quick learning Engineer. I love to learn.

Work experience

Blockchain Developer

August 2020 - July 2021

Blocverse (Blockchain services Company)

- Developed secure smart contracts using Solidity.
- Writing tests for the smart contracts with Mocha and Chai.
- Deploying secure smart contracts to the Polygon Network.
- Ensuring Gas Optimization to prevent high gas fees.
- Interacting with the deployed smart contract from the blockchain using Ethers.js and Web3.js in the frontend application.

Backend Developer

September 2019 - August 2020

Mismo Solutions (IT Services and Consulting Company)

- Developing software in a variety of languages and frameworks such as Node.JS.
- Diagnosing and resolving application faults.
- Generating comprehensive test plans.
- Designing and implementing quality, scalable web-based software products.
- Analyzing user requirements.
- Supporting existing software products and making progress on new products.
- Develop and design RESTful services and APIs.

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology

2021 - 2022

Middlesex University London

Graduated with First Class Honors

Advance Diploma in Software Engineering (ADSE)

2017 - 2019

Aptech Computer Education, Enugu, Nigeria.

Graduated with Distinction.

Cerificate for participating in Techwiz, Aptech students global competition.

Senior School Certificate

2011 - 2017

King's College Lagos

Distinction in Mathematics and Computer Studies.

Technologies

- Solidity
- Truffle
- Node.is
- React.js
- HTML and CSS
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- Git
- Ethers.js
- Web3.js
- Hardhat
- Openzeppelin

Github profile

https://github.com/godwintrav

Linkedln

https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwinodenigbo-251755174/